// questions list



let questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "From this Italian City, which one is the most touristic?",
        answer: "Rome",
        options: [
            "Milan",
            "Rome",
            "Venice",
            "Pisa"
        ]

    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: " What is the most used Mobile App in France in 2021?",
        answer: "CovidApp",
        options: [
            "Netflix",
            "Disney+",
            "Tinder",
            "CovidApp"]

    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: " How old is the Oldest living French person?",
        answer: "118",
        options: [
            "108",
            "110",
            "118",
            "120"]
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: " What mountain range forms the northern border of Italy?",
        answer: "Alps",
        options: [
            "Rochies",
            "Alps",
            "Macaroni",
            "None"]

    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: " How long is the Dutch coastline?",
        answer: "451km",
        options: [
            "351km",
            "451km",
            "499km",
            "562km"]
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: " What country is the biggest (surface?)",
        answer: "France",
        options: [
            "France",
            "Germany",
            "Spain",
            "Italy"]

    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: " Which of these things are no strict social rules in Italy?",
        answer: "Punctuality",
        options: [
            "Business Relations",
            "Giving Gifts",
            "Punctuality",
            "Greetings"]



    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: "  What is NOT a Christian holiday in NL?",
        answer: "King's Day",
        options: [
            "Easter",
            "Ascension",
            "Pentecost",
            "King's Day"]

    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: "   What is Italyâ€™s shape similar to?",
        answer: "A boot",
        options: [
            "A mountain",
            "A dog",
            "A boot",
            "A dragon"]

    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: "When is France National day?",
        answer: "July 14th",
        options: [
            "Jan 3rd",
            "March 15th",
            "July 14th",
            "Oct 10th"]


    }
];

